const lessons = [
  {
    title: 'Introduction to Portuguese',
    content: 'Welcome to the basic Portuguese course. Learn greetings and simple phrases.',
    flashcards: [
      { question: 'How do you say "Hello" in Portuguese?', answer: 'Olá' },
      { question: 'How do you say "Thank you" in Portuguese?', answer: 'Obrigado(a)' },
    ],
    quiz: [
      { question: '1) What is the Portuguese word for "Goodbye"?', options: ['Adeus', 'Olá', 'Obrigado(a)'], correctAnswer: 'Adeus' },
      { question: '2) How do you say "Please" in Portuguese?', options: ['Por favor', 'Obrigado(a)', 'De nada'], correctAnswer: 'Por favor' },
      { question: '3) What is the Portuguese word for "Yes"?', options: ['Sim', 'Não', 'Talvez'], correctAnswer: 'Sim' },
      { question: '4) What is the Portuguese word for "No"?', options: ['Sim', 'Não', 'Talvez'], correctAnswer: 'Não' },
      { question: '5) How do you say "Thank you" in Portuguese?', options: ['Obrigado(a)', 'Olá', 'Por favor'], correctAnswer: 'Obrigado(a)' },
      { question: '6) What is the Portuguese word for "Excuse me"?', options: ['Com licença', 'Desculpe', 'Por favor'], correctAnswer: 'Com licença' },
      { question: '7) What is the Portuguese word for "How are you?"', options: ['Como vai?', 'Onde está?', 'O que é?'], correctAnswer: 'Como vai?' },
      { question: '8) How do you say "Good morning" in Portuguese?', options: ['Bom dia', 'Boa noite', 'Boa tarde'], correctAnswer: 'Bom dia' },
      { question: '9) How do you say "Good night" in Portuguese?', options: ['Boa noite', 'Bom dia', 'Boa tarde'], correctAnswer: 'Boa noite' },
      { question: '10) How do you say "See you later" in Portuguese?', options: ['Até logo', 'Bom dia', 'Adeus'], correctAnswer: 'Até logo' },
      { question: '11) How do you say "How much is this?" in Portuguese?', options: ['Quanto custa?', 'Onde está?', 'Como vai?'], correctAnswer: 'Quanto custa?' },
      { question: '12) How do you say "What time is it?" in Portuguese?', options: ['Que horas são?', 'Onde fica?', 'O que é isso?'], correctAnswer: 'Que horas são?' },
      { question: '13) How do you say "I don\'t understand" in Portuguese?', options: ['Eu não entendo', 'Eu entendo', 'Não sei'], correctAnswer: 'Eu não entendo' },
      { question: '14) How do you say "Where is the bathroom?" in Portuguese?', options: ['Onde fica o banheiro?', 'Onde está?', 'Como você vai?'], correctAnswer: 'Onde fica o banheiro?' },
      { question: '15) How do you say "I need help" in Portuguese?', options: ['Eu preciso de ajuda', 'Eu posso ajudar', 'Eu entendo'], correctAnswer: 'Eu preciso de ajuda' },
      
    ]
  }
];

export default lessons;
